And another thing, the bank want to see your trust
and the bank should be the only one seeing your trust.
Your life estate is real estate.
It's literally a movable property,
which means you cannot own it.
You can only have interest in it.
Your trust should be a non grantor
irrevocable living trust where your birth certificate name is not trusty.
Once you understand that
the birth certificate name has retired from the world of commerce,
you can peacefully receive your interest and principle like you supposed to,
but it's ultimately because you no longer trading with the enemy.
Over here we talk about money of account, not money of exchange.